<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
  <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>3.11</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>RoboSoft 4.0.756</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>http://robosoft.rudenko.com</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used
      by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software
      products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
  </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
  <RoboSoft>
    <Company_UIN>CMP-00551AFE9C7</Company_UIN>
    <Company_Description>KARPOLAN is a nickname of Anton Karpenko</Company_Description>
    <Product_UIN>APP-00B91BE1080</Product_UIN>
    <Search_String>Keyboard LEDs</Search_String>
    <Press_Release_Search_String>Keyboard LEDs</Press_Release_Search_String>
    <NewsFeed_Search_String>Keyboard LEDs</NewsFeed_Search_String>
    <Search_Engine_Search_String>Keyboard LEDs</Search_Engine_Search_String>
    <Web_Directories_Search_String>Keyboard LEDs</Web_Directories_Search_String>
    <Search_String_Unique>KARPOLAN</Search_String_Unique>
    <Comments_For_Reviewer>Thank you for your interest. Hope this program helps you too :)</Comments_For_Reviewer>
    <Publish_on_CD>TRUE</Publish_on_CD>
    <Backlink>https://keyboard-leds.com/submit.html</Backlink>
    <RSProductType></RSProductType>
  </RoboSoft>
  <Company_Info>
    <Company_Name>KARPOLAN</Company_Name>
    <Address_1>#101 - 1001 W. Broadway, 381</Address_1>
    <Address_2></Address_2>
    <City_Town>Vancouver</City_Town>
    <State_Province>BC</State_Province>
    <Zip_Postal_Code>V6H 4E4</Zip_Postal_Code>
    <Country>Canada</Country>
    <Company_WebSite_URL>https://karpolan.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
    <Contact_Info>
      <Contact_First_Name>Anton</Contact_First_Name>
      <Contact_Last_Name>Karpenko</Contact_Last_Name>
      <Contact_Email>pad@karpolan.com</Contact_Email>
      <Author_First_Name>Anton</Author_First_Name>
      <Author_Last_Name>Karpenko</Author_Last_Name>
      <Author_Email>pad@karpolan.com</Author_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
    <Support_Info>
      <Sales_Email>pad@karpolan.com</Sales_Email>
      <Support_Email>pad@karpolan.com</Support_Email>
      <General_Email>pad@karpolan.com</General_Email>
      <Sales_Phone>38 093 3944815</Sales_Phone>
      <Support_Phone>38 093 3944815</Support_Phone>
      <General_Phone>38 093 3944815</General_Phone>
      <Fax_Phone>38 093 3944815</Fax_Phone>
    </Support_Info>
  </Company_Info>
  <ASP>
    <ASP_FORM>Y</ASP_FORM>
    <ASP_Member>Y</ASP_Member>
    <ASP_Member_Number>04242</ASP_Member_Number>
  </ASP>
  <NewsFeed>
    <NewsFeed_FORM>Y</NewsFeed_FORM>
    <NewsFeed_VERSION>1.0</NewsFeed_VERSION>
    <NewsFeed_URL>http://Submit-Everywhere.com/extensions/NewsFeed.htm</NewsFeed_URL>
    <NewsFeed_DESCRIPTION>This PAD extension allows you to add your RSS and Atom news feeds info
      into your PAD file. This info can be used by RSS feed submission software or by feed
      directories themselves.</NewsFeed_DESCRIPTION>
    <NewsFeed_Type>RSS 0.90</NewsFeed_Type>
    <NewsFeed_Language>English</NewsFeed_Language>
    <NewsFeed_Purpose>News</NewsFeed_Purpose>
    <NewsFeed_Author_Email>pad@karpolan.com</NewsFeed_Author_Email>
    <NewsFeed_Author_First_Name>Anton</NewsFeed_Author_First_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Author_Last_Name>Karpenko</NewsFeed_Author_Last_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Feed_URL>https://keyboard-leds.com/feed/</NewsFeed_Feed_URL>
    <NewsFeed_Site_Name>Keyboard LEDs</NewsFeed_Site_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Site_URL>https://keyboard-leds.com/</NewsFeed_Site_URL>
    <NewsFeed_Title>Keyboard LEDs</NewsFeed_Title>
    <NewsFeed_Description_70>Keyboard Leds software lets you know the current state of keyboard loc</NewsFeed_Description_70>
    <NewsFeed_Description_250>Keyboard Leds software lets you know the current state of keyboard
      locks</NewsFeed_Description_250>
  </NewsFeed>
  <Site>
    <Site_FORM>Y</Site_FORM>
    <Site_VERSION>1.0</Site_VERSION>
    <Site_URL>http://Submit-Everywhere.com/extensions/Site.htm</Site_URL>
    <Site_DESCRIPTION>This PAD extension allows you to add your site info into your PAD file. This
      info can be used by site submission software or by web directories themselves.</Site_DESCRIPTION>
    <Site_Contact_Email>pad@karpolan.com</Site_Contact_Email>
    <Site_Contact_First_Name>Anton</Site_Contact_First_Name>
    <Site_Contact_Last_Name>Karpenko</Site_Contact_Last_Name>
    <Site_Site_Title>Keyboard LEDs</Site_Site_Title>
    <Site_Site_URL>https://keyboard-leds.com/</Site_Site_URL>
    <Site_Description_100>Keyboard Leds software lets you know the current state of keyboard locks</Site_Description_100>
    <Site_Description_250>Keyboard Leds software lets you know the current state of keyboard locks.
      You can see the status either on a small icon in the system tray or on a floating OSD window.</Site_Description_250>
    <Site_Description_450>Lots of notebooks, netbooks and cordless keyboards have no indicators for
      Caps Lock, and Num Lock. Scroll Lock's bulb disappeared almost from any hardware for now.
      Keyboard Leds software solves this problem. The program lets you know the current state of
      keyboard locks. You can see the status either on a small icon in the system tray or on a
      floating OSD window.</Site_Description_450>
    <Site_Keywords>caps lock, num lock, scroll lock, keyboard lock, keyboard indicator, keyboard
      led, lock indicator. shift lock</Site_Keywords>
  </Site>
  <ASBMPlannerID1stRound>10</ASBMPlannerID1stRound>
  <Issues>13</Issues>
  <ASBMPlannerID2ndRound>11</ASBMPlannerID2ndRound>
  <Program_Info>
    <Program_Name>Keyboard LEDs</Program_Name>
    <Program_Version>2.71</Program_Version>
    <Program_Release_Month>09</Program_Release_Month>
    <Program_Release_Day>06</Program_Release_Day>
    <Program_Release_Year>2012</Program_Release_Year>
    <Program_Cost_Dollars>0.00</Program_Cost_Dollars>
    <Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
    <Program_Release_Status>Minor Update</Program_Release_Status>
    <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
    <Program_OS_Support>WinXP,WinVista,WinVista x64,Win7 x32,Win7
      x64,Win2000,WinServer,Win98,WinME,WinNT 4.x</Program_OS_Support>
    <Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
    <Program_Change_Info>Added option to disable Internet features (updates, PingNotify statistics,
      etc.) Memory consumption improved.</Program_Change_Info>
    <Program_System_Requirements>none</Program_System_Requirements>
    <Program_Category_Class>System Utilities::Automation Tools</Program_Category_Class>
    <File_Info>
      <File_Size_Bytes>522508</File_Size_Bytes>
      <File_Size_K>510</File_Size_K>
      <File_Size_MB>0.50</File_Size_MB>
      <Filename_Versioned></Filename_Versioned>
      <Filename_Previous></Filename_Previous>
      <Filename_Generic></Filename_Generic>
      <Filename_Long></Filename_Long>
    </File_Info>
    <Expire_Info>
      <Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
      <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
      <Expire_Count></Expire_Count>
      <Expire_Other_Info></Expire_Other_Info>
      <Expire_Month></Expire_Month>
      <Expire_Day></Expire_Day>
      <Expire_Year></Expire_Year>
    </Expire_Info>
    <Program_Categories>
      num lock,caps
      lock,keyboard,indicator,enhancment,System,Desktop,mouse,Utilities,tools,Software,Notebook,Computer,windows,misc</Program_Categories>
    <Limitations>none</Limitations>
    <Awards>Many from other web archives</Awards>
    <Program_Cost_Other_Code></Program_Cost_Other_Code>
    <Program_Cost_Other></Program_Cost_Other>
    <Program_Specific_Category></Program_Specific_Category>
    <Includes_JAVA_VM></Includes_JAVA_VM>
    <Includes_VB_Runtime></Includes_VB_Runtime>
    <Includes_DirectX></Includes_DirectX>
  </Program_Info>
  <Web_Info>
    <Application_URLs>
      <Application_Info_URL>htts://keyboard-leds.com</Application_Info_URL>
      <Application_Order_URL>https://keyboard-leds.com/download/</Application_Order_URL>
      <Application_Screenshot_URL>https://keyboard-leds.com/images/screenshot.png</Application_Screenshot_URL>
      <Application_Icon_URL>https://keyboard-leds.com/images/icon-32x32.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
      <Application_XML_File_URL>https://keyboard-leds.com/pad.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
    <Download_URLs>
      <Primary_Download_URL>https://keyboard-leds.com/files/keyboard-leds.exe</Primary_Download_URL>
      <Secondary_Download_URL>https://keyboard-leds.com/files/keyboard-leds.zip</Secondary_Download_URL>
      <Additional_Download_URL_1></Additional_Download_URL_1>
      <Additional_Download_URL_2></Additional_Download_URL_2>
    </Download_URLs>
  </Web_Info>
  <Permissions>
    <Distribution_Permissions>This Software may be distributed freely through on-line services,
      bulletin boards, or other forms of electronic media, as long as the files are distributed in
      their entirety. Computer Magazines/Archives are authorized to distribute Software on any Cover
      Disk or CD-ROM without an individual permission.</Distribution_Permissions>
    <EULA>This is the End User License Agreement (the "Agreement") is a legal agreement between you,
      the end-user ("Licensee"), and KARPOLAN, the manufacturer and the copyright owner ("Owner"),
      for the use of the "Keyboard Leds" aka "Keyboard Indicators" aka "Key Leds" software product
      ("Software").

      By using this Software or storing this program on a computer drive (or other media), you are
      agreeing to be bound by the terms of this Agreement. If you do not agree with the terms of
      this Agreement, please remove this Software from your system.


      Rights
      ======

      The Software is protected by copyright laws and international copyright treaties, as well as
      other intellectual property laws and treaties. Software is licensed, not sold. Software is
      free to use and includes no technical support. The origin of this Software must not be
      misrepresented.


      Copyright
      =========

      All title, including but not limited to copyrights, in and to the Software and any copies
      thereof are owned by Owner or its suppliers. All title and intellectual property rights in and
      to the content which may be accessed through use of the Software is the property of the
      respective content owner and may be protected by applicable copyright or other intellectual
      property laws and treaties. This Agreement grants you no rights to use such content. All
      rights not expressly granted are reserved by Owner.


      Distribution
      ============

      This Software may be distributed freely through on-line services, bulletin boards, or other
      forms of electronic media, as long as the files are distributed in their entirety. Computer
      Magazines/Archives are authorized to distribute Software on any Cover Disk or CD-ROM without
      an individual permission.


      Restrictions
      ============

      You may not alter this Software in any way, including changing or removing any messages or
      windows. You may not decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble or otherwise reduce this
      Software to a human perceivable form. You may not modify, rent or resell this Software for
      profit, or create any derivative works, based upon this Software.


      Disclaimer
      ==========

      This Software is provided on an "as is" basis without warranty of any kind, expressed or
      implied, including but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability and
      suitability for a particular purpose. The person using the Software bears all risk as to the
      quality and performance of the Software. Owner will not be liable for any special, incidental,
      consequential, indirect or similar damages due to loss of data or any other reason, even if
      Owner or an agent of Owner has been advised of the possibility of such damages. In no event
      will Owner be liable for costs of any damages. You acknowledge that you have read this
      license, understood it, and agreed to be bound by its terms.</EULA>
  </Permissions>
  <Program_Descriptions>
    <English>
      <Keywords>caps lock, num lock, scroll lock, keyboard lock, keyboard indicator, keyboard led,
        lock indicator. shift lock</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Lets you know the state of keyboard locks</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Keyboard Leds software lets you know the current state of keyboard locks</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Keyboard Leds software lets you know the current state of keyboard locks. You
        can see the status either on a small icon in the system tray or on a floating OSD window.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Lots of notebooks, netbooks and cordless keyboards have no indicators for Caps
        Lock, and Num Lock. Scroll Lock's bulb disappeared almost from any hardware for now.
        Keyboard Leds software solves this problem. The program lets you know the current state of
        keyboard locks. You can see the status either on a small icon in the system tray or on a
        floating OSD window.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Lots of notebooks, netbooks and cordless keyboards have no indicators for Caps
        Lock, and Num Lock. Scroll Lock's bulb disappeared almost from any hardware for now.
        Keyboard Leds software solves this problem. The program lets you know the current state of
        keyboard locks. You can see the status either on a small icon in the system tray or on a
        floating OSD window.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </English>
    <Russian>
      <Char_Desc_2000>На многих современных ноутбуках, нетбуках и беспроводных клавиатурах
        отсутствуют светодиодные индикаторы Caps Lock и Num Lock. А о лампочке Scroll Lock
        производители забыли уже давно. Программа Keyboard Leds решает эту проблему, с помощью ее Вы
        можете узнать текущее состояние переключателей клавиатуры. Положение "замков" отображается
        на иконке в системном лотке, а так же в плавающем окне на экране.</Char_Desc_2000>
      <Char_Desc_450>На многих современных ноутбуках, нетбуках и беспроводных клавиатурах
        отсутствуют светодиодные индикаторы Caps Lock и Num Lock. А о лампочке Scroll Lock
        производители забыли уже давно. Программа Keyboard Leds решает эту проблему, с помощью ее Вы
        можете узнать текущее состояние переключателей клавиатуры. Положение "замков" отображается
        на иконке в системном лотке, а так же в плавающем окне на экране.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_250>Keyboard Leds позволяет узнать текущее состояние переключателей клавиатуры.
        Состояние светодиодов отображается на иконке в системном лотке а так же в плавающем окне на
        экране.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_80>Keyboard Leds позволяет узнать текущее состояние переключателей клавиатуры</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_45>Текущее состояние переключателей клавиатуры</Char_Desc_45>
      <Keywords>клавиатура, keyboard, caps lock, num lock, scroll lock</Keywords>
    </Russian>
    <German>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Viele Notebooks, Netbooks und schnurlose Tastaturen haben keine Indikatoren
        für Caps Lock, Num Lock und. Scroll Lock's Birne verschwand fast von jeder Hardware für
        jetzt. Keyboard Leds Software löst dieses Problem. Das Programm lässt Sie wissen, den
        aktuellen Stand der Tastatur sperrt. Sie können den Status entweder auf ein kleines Symbol
        in der Taskleiste oder auf einer schwimmenden OSD-Fenster zu sehen.</Char_Desc_2000>
      <Char_Desc_450>Viele Notebooks, Netbooks und schnurlose Tastaturen haben keine Indikatoren für
        Caps Lock, Num Lock und. Scroll Lock's Birne verschwand fast von jeder Hardware für jetzt.
        Keyboard Leds Software löst dieses Problem. Das Programm lässt Sie wissen, den aktuellen
        Stand der Tastatur sperrt. Sie können den Status entweder auf ein kleines Symbol in der
        Taskleiste oder auf einer schwimmenden OSD-Fenster zu sehen.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_250>Keyboard Leds Software können Sie den aktuellen Stand der Tastatur sperrt. Sie
        können den Status entweder auf ein kleines Symbol in der Taskleiste oder auf einer
        schwimmenden OSD-Fenster zu sehen.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_80>Software können Sie den aktuellen Stand der Tastatur sperrt</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_45>Sie den aktuellen Stand der Tastatur sperrt</Char_Desc_45>
      <Keywords>tastatur, keyboard, caps lock, num lock, scroll lock</Keywords>
    </German>
    <French>
      <Keywords>clavier, keyboard, caps lock, num lock, scroll lock</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Actuel des écluses du clavier</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Logiciel vous permet de connaître l'état actuel des écluses du clavier</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Keyboard Leds logiciel vous permet de connaître l'état actuel des écluses du
        clavier. Vous pouvez voir l'état soit sur une petite icône dans la barre système ou sur une
        fenêtre flottante OSD.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Beaucoup de portables, netbooks et des claviers sans fil ont pas d'indicateurs
        pour les Caps Lock, Num Lock et. ampoule Scroll Lock a disparu presque de tout le matériel
        pour le moment. Keyboard Leds logiciel résout ce problème. Le programme vous permet de
        connaître l'état actuel des écluses du clavier. Vous pouvez voir l'état soit sur une petite
        icône dans la barre système ou sur une fenêtre flottante OSD.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Beaucoup de portables, netbooks et des claviers sans fil ont pas d'indicateurs
        pour les Caps Lock, Num Lock et. ampoule Scroll Lock a disparu presque de tout le matériel
        pour le moment. Keyboard Leds logiciel résout ce problème. Le programme vous permet de
        connaître l'état actuel des écluses du clavier. Vous pouvez voir l'état soit sur une petite
        icône dans la barre système ou sur une fenêtre flottante OSD.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </French>
    <Spanish>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Muchos de los portátiles, netbooks y teclados inalámbricos no tienen
        indicadores de bloqueo de mayúsculas, bloqueo numérico y. bulbo Scroll Lock desapareció casi
        desde cualquier hardware por ahora. Keyboard Leds de software resuelve este problema. El
        programa le permite conocer el estado actual de bloqueos de teclado. Usted puede ver el
        estado ya sea en un pequeño icono en la bandeja del sistema o en una ventana flotante OSD.</Char_Desc_2000>
      <Char_Desc_450>Muchos de los portátiles, netbooks y teclados inalámbricos no tienen
        indicadores de bloqueo de mayúsculas, bloqueo numérico y. bulbo Scroll Lock desapareció casi
        desde cualquier hardware por ahora. Keyboard Leds de software resuelve este problema. El
        programa le permite conocer el estado actual de bloqueos de teclado. Usted puede ver el
        estado ya sea en un pequeño icono en la bandeja del sistema o en una ventana flotante OSD.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_250>Keyboard Leds le permite conocer el estado actual de bloqueos de teclado. Usted
        puede ver el estado ya sea en un pequeño icono en la bandeja del sistema o en una ventana
        flotante OSD.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_45>El estado actual de bloqueos de teclado</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Keyboard Leds le permite conocer el estado actual de bloqueos de teclado</Char_Desc_80>
      <Keywords>teclado, keyboard, caps lock, num lock, scroll lock</Keywords>
    </Spanish>
    <Italian>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Lots di notebook, netbook e tastiere senza fili non hanno indicatori di Caps
        Lock e Bloc Num. Bulbo Scroll Lock è scomparso quasi da qualsiasi hardware, per ora. I led
        della tastiera software risolve questo problema. Il programma ti permette di conoscere lo
        stato attuale delle serrature tastiera. È possibile visualizzare lo stato o su una piccola
        icona nella system tray o su una finestra OSD mobile.</Char_Desc_2000>
      <Char_Desc_450>Lots di notebook, netbook e tastiere senza fili non hanno indicatori di Caps
        Lock e Bloc Num. Bulbo Scroll Lock è scomparso quasi da qualsiasi hardware, per ora. I led
        della tastiera software risolve questo problema. Il programma ti permette di conoscere lo
        stato attuale delle serrature tastiera. È possibile visualizzare lo stato o su una piccola
        icona nella system tray o su una finestra OSD mobile.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_250>Keyboard Leds software ti permette di conoscere lo stato attuale delle
        serrature tastiera. È possibile visualizzare lo stato o su una piccola icona nella system
        tray o su una finestra OSD mobile.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_80>Software ti permette di conoscere lo stato attuale delle serrature tastiera</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_45>Consente di conoscere lo stato della tastiera</Char_Desc_45>
      <Keywords>Caps Lock, Bloc Num, Scroll Lock, blocco tastiera, Indicatore della tastiera,
        tastiera led, indicatore di blocco. shift lock</Keywords>
    </Italian>
    <Portuguese>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Os lotes de notebooks, netbooks e teclados sem fio não tem indicadores para
        CapsLock e Num Lock. Bulbo Scroll Lock desapareceu quase de qualquer hardware por enquanto.
        Keyboard Leds software resolve esse problema. O programa permite quevocê saiba o estado
        atual da trava o teclado. Você pode ver o status, quer por umpequeno ícone na bandeja do
        sistema ou em uma janela OSD flutuante.</Char_Desc_2000>
      <Char_Desc_450>Os lotes de notebooks, netbooks e teclados sem fio não tem indicadores para
        CapsLock e Num Lock. Bulbo Scroll Lock desapareceu quase de qualquer hardware por enquanto.
        Keyboard Leds software resolve esse problema. O programa permite quevocê saiba o estado
        atual da trava o teclado. Você pode ver o status, quer por umpequeno ícone na bandeja do
        sistema ou em uma janela OSD flutuante.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_250>Keyboard Leds software permite que você saiba o estado atual da trava o
        teclado.Você pode ver o status, quer por um pequeno ícone na bandeja do sistema ou em
        umajanela OSD flutuante.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_80>Keyboard Leds software permite que você saiba o estado atual do teclado bloqueia</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_45>Você saiba o estado da trava o teclado</Char_Desc_45>
      <Keywords>caps lock, num lock, scroll lock, bloqueio de teclado, indicador de teclado, teclado
        conduzida</Keywords>
    </Portuguese>
  </Program_Descriptions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>